Fedor

Ivachev



Contact

GitHub:

github.com/FedorIvachev

WeChat:

rod_iv

Email:

rod iv@outlook.com

Languages

English – C1 Chinese – A2 Russian – native

Hobbies

- Hiking
- Photography
- Mobile industry research

Summary

Junior Computer Graphics Developer. Has strong background in competitive programming, physics and math. Has developed and published Apps for iOS, Android and Tizen OS. Has experience in Deep learning.

Programming Languages: C++, Python (writing regularly), Swift, C#, Java, JavaScript, Haskell (have experience).

Tools, Libraries: **Git, OpenCV, Machine learning libraries, OpenGL, Graphics Profilers, Unity**

Experience

Software Engineer - 02/2019 to 08/2019 **Huawei Technologies Co., Ltd**, Moscow

Work on the low-level Graphic Profiling Tools.

Intern- 06/2018 to 09/2018 **Samsung RC, Ltd**, Moscow

• Develop computer vision algorithms in 3D Avatar team.

Education

Bachelor in Applied Mathematics and Computer Science: Computer Algebra – 2015-2019 Lomonosov Moscow State University, Moscow, Russia

Master in Computer Science:

Advanced Computing – HCI – 2019-2021 **Tsinghua University**, Beijing, China

Certifications

Certificates of Summer Programming School (2012, 2013, 2014), Kostroma, Russia

Top 100 at All-Russian Olympiad of Programming, 2014 Certificate of Practice in Web Apps Development, Samsung RC, Ltd, 2017

Scholarships

Full tuition for Lomonosov MSU Business School, 2018 Chinese Government Scholarship, 2019

Publications

Modification of Algorithm for inverting matrices with elements from ring of scalar differential operators, Best Thesises 2019, CMC MSU